geekmontage.com 2016-10-11

# Privacy Policy | Geek Montage

## Privacy Policy

Last Updated on Tuesday, 9 November 2010 12:21 Written by DarkKnightH20 Wednesday, 1 September 2010 07:24

(last update: Sep 2010)

### Information we gather

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address  
Country  
Referrer

### How we use the information we gather

We use the information to see statistical information about where our visitors are coming from and who they are.

### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by nobody

### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we keep it password protected and delete it once its been of use

### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

This entry was posted on Wednesday, September 1st, 2010 at 7:24 AM and is filed under . You can follow any responses to this entry through the [RSS 2.0](http://geekmontage.com/sitemap/privacy-policy/feed/) feed. You can leave a response, or [trackback](http://geekmontage.com/sitemap/privacy-policy/trackback/) from your own site.
